guys I'm tired do you think we can stop
to rest and I have to go pee will you
two just shut up already
Sonic you just pooped behind that tree
three minutes ago hey guys
does that tree look a little bit off to
you guys yet why is it Orange
it smells kind of weird too bro is that
where you crapped
Oh God Sonia Sonic please please help me
wait a Mobius minute that's not a tree
that's Dingo too little too late
your brother is mine now he's crushing
me bro
says you have to do something let him
bow
you your brother's life is now in
sir Robotnik's hands if you make any
sudden movements I will kill him right
here dammit
is there really nothing we can do my boy
you better unhand my boy right now they
it's feral what is feral doing here what
the hell is that the stink bug I
had a dream my boy and that dream it
said to come help you here
amazing could it be that the Oracle of
Delphi us gave you a vision of the
future it just might be fate that you
would join us war two outnumbered here
Sleet maybe we should fall back now we
already have one of them in our clutches
you failed
ding face or well one is good enough for
now let's go
someone stop them they're going to take
my bro
I don't think so ass oh no Sleet
are you okay how could you hurt him he
was my best friend I'll kill all of you
burn in hell where you belong burn
sorry to say my boy but this is where
you run that is if you know what's good
for you I got my boy Manic quick let's
get out of here no it can't be like this
I will destroy you damn it please Ling
go let them go they won this battle
they always win it looks like we
lost and for now let's get out of here
before they come looking for us again
yeah let's make like a banana and split
before that I think you should all take
a look at this it's a note but from who
sips something tells me we have a big
adventure ahead of us hold on to your
butt cheeks